(Sheldon:)It's like living
with a lactose-intolerant parrot.
(Leonard:)Trust me. Call her.
(Amy:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)It's a shame you didn't go
to dinner with us...
(Sheldon:)...because the buffet you're about to enjoy
only serves humble pie...
(Sheldon:)...a dessert much less tasty
than frozen yogurt.
(Sheldon:)I was this close.
(Amy(on skype):)What?
(Sheldon:)You'll appreciate this.
(Sheldon:)Leonard has some ridiculous notion
that you're mad at me.
(Sheldon:)Tell him you're not mad at me.
Go ahead, set him straight.
(Amy:)I'm mad at you, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Hmm...
(Sheldon:)Eat one of your Luna Bars.
(Sheldon:)Very often, when women think
they're angry, they're really just hungry.
(Amy:)I'm not hungry.
(Amy:)Your friend insulted me
and you didn't do anything.
(Sheldon:)Precisely. I didn't do anything.
(Sheldon:)Now, does someone feel like checking
her emotional math?